iklipz.com 2007-10-11

# iKlipz See - Show - Share

About iklipz.com  
iklipz.com is an online service that allows our members to set up unique personal profiles that can be linked together through networks of friends. iklipz members can view iklipz content, each others' profiles, communicate with old friends and meet new friends on the service, share photos, post journals and comments, and describe their interests. To enrich our members' experience, we request and display some personal information to other members and visitors, which allows our users to identify each other and expand their network of friends. iklipz members can change their profile information at any time and can control how other members and the service communicates with them. 

iklipz.com cares deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at [cs@iklipz.com](mailto:cs@iklipz.com).

Information Collection and Use by iklipz.com  
iklipz.com collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the iklipz.com service. iklipz.com also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other. iklipz.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes 

User Profile information including members' pictures and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the iklipz.com social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join iklipz, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network Users within a personal network communicate on iklipz.com with each other through the iklipz.com service, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, iklipz.com allows users to search for other members using first and last name, email address, and schools and/or companies where users may have attended or worked. We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by changing their "notification" setting to "Do not send me notification emails" in the user "Account Settings" From time to time, iklipz.com or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on iklipz.com. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

Invitations and Other Communications to Non-members  
iklipz members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. iklipz.com stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations iklipz.com does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations, invitation reminders . Recipients of invitations from iklipz.com may contact iklipz.com to request the removal of their information from our database. iklipz members may also store email addresses of people they know in their internal iklipz address book and may also choose to send invitations and other communications to those addresses. You may prevent iklipz.com email invitations and other messages from being sent to any email address you control by sending a single email with the subject "BLOCK" to [cs@iklipz.com](mailto:cs@iklipz.com) Please note that the email must come from the account you wish to block.

Use of Cookies  
iklipz.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from iklipz.com in order to use most functions on the site Please note that iklipz allows 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the iklipz Privacy Policy.

Links  
iklipz.com contains links to sites. iklipz.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on iklipz.com.

Chat Rooms, Journals and WebLogs, Message Boards, Classifieds and Public Forums  
Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to Journals, WebLogs, Message Boards, Classifieds or any other Public Forums that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

Correcting/Updating or Removing Information  
iklipz.com users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Info.

Email Choice/Opt-out  
Members who no longer wish to receive updates or notifications may choose not to by selecting 'Do not send me notification emails' in the user profile 'Account Settings'. Users who do not wish to receive iklipz.com newsletters may choose not to by selecting 'Do not send me iklipz newsletters' in the user profile 'Account Settings'. All notification emails and iklipz.com newsletters also include the above instructions for opting-out of those communications in the future.

Information for California Users of iklipz  
If you are a resident of the State of California, under the California Civil Code, you have the right to request, from companies conducting business in California, a list of all third parties to which the company has disclosed Personal Information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that if the company has a Privacy Statement that gives either an opt-out (which we may sometimes refer to as "unsubscribe") or opt-in choice for use of your Personal Information by third parties (such as advertisers or affiliated companies) for marketing purposes, the company may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options. When you "opt-in" it means you are giving and granting us your consent and approval for the transaction, exchange of information, communication or other activity described in the opt-in process or the terms and conditions that apply to your opt-in. You should read our Terms of Use carefully since there are times and situations in which your use of the iklipz Network constitutes your consent and approval (hence your "opt-in"). iklipz qualifies for the alternative option. iklipz has a comprehensive Privacy Statement and provides you with details on how you may either opt-out or opt-in to the use of your Personal Information by third parties for direct marketing purposes. Therefore, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of the third parties that received your Personal Information for marketing purposes during the preceding year.

Parents of Underaged Users  
**iklipz is solely for users 14 years old and older.** Anyone using iklipz that is less than age 14 is in violation of iklipz policy and by doing so expressly grants to their legal guardian the right to access all personal information about the underaged users’ account. Parents (including legal guardians) of children that registered on the Ikilpz Network in violation of the [TERMS OF USE] who wish to terminate their child's Registration must send us an e-mail at [cs@iklipz.com](mailto:cs@iklipz.com) and provide us with their child's User ID or alternatively, a parent must provide verifiable identification that they are the parent of the ineligible child. Children under the age of fourteen [14] that are unknowingly registered on the iklipz Network are in violation of our Terms Of Use. We will not allow direct access to a user's registration and Personal Information by any person without the user's User ID (Please see above for how to change your preferences or the information associated with your account). If a parent does not have his or her child's User ID, the parent will be required to send an e-mail to the Privacy Administrator at [cs@iklipz.com](mailto:cs@iklipz.com) that includes the parent's name, address, telephone and e-mail address, in addition to the child's name and e-mail address associated with the child's User ID registered on the iklipz Network, plus the child's date of birth. iklipz will send a confirming e-mail to the parent via the e-mail address provided to verify that the parent wishes to terminate his or her child's registration. The parent must then confirm by sending a reply e-mail to the designated return address. iklipz will then terminate the child's account but will notify the child of the termination request via e-mail and will identify the name, address and e-mail address of the person making the request.

Third Party Advertising  
Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by iklipz.com or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by iklipz.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Security  
iklipz.com member accounts are secured by member-created passwords iklipz.com takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time For any additional information about the security measures we use on iklipz.com, please contact us at [cs@iklipz.com](mailto:cs@iklipz.com)

Sharing and Disclosure of Information iklipz.com Collects  
Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, iklipz will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by iklipz.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the iklipz.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. iklipz reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of iklipz or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.

Changes in Our Privacy Policy  
From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

Contacting the Web Site   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: [cs@iklipz.com](mailto:cs@iklipz.com) 8447 Wilshire Blvd Suite 102 Beverly Hills, CA 90211.
